[
    {
        "Question": "q1",
        "Response": "COMB",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "WEDNESDAY",
        "Count": 2
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "CANADA",
        "Count": 4
    },
    {
        "Question": "q1",
        "Response": "BRUSH",
        "Count": 5
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "JAPAN",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q1",
        "Response": "PHONE",
        "Count": 2
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "TUESDAY",
        "Count": 5
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "PHILIDELPHIA",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "CAMBODIA",
        "Count": 3
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "FRIDAY",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q1",
        "Response": "TOILET",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "SUNDAY",
        "Count": 2
    },
    {
        "Question": "q1",
        "Response": "WALK",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "CROACIA",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q1",
        "Response": "TOOTHBRUSH",
        "Count": 2
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "THURSDAY",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "NORWAY",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "SATURDAY",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q3",
        "Response": "ITALY",
        "Count": 1
    },
    {
        "Question": "q2",
        "Response": "MONDAY",
        "Count": 1
    }
]